A Guide to the Governor George C. Peery Executive records, 1934-1938
Library of Virginia
- Series I. General Correspondence, 1934-1938., Extent: 46 cu. ft. [92 boxes]. (Box 1-92)
  - Monroe Birthplace Monument Association (Box 65)
  - Mother's Day (Box 65)
  - Motion Picture Censors Board (Box 65)
  - Motor Safety (Box 65-66)
  - Motor Vehicles (Box 66)
  - Motor Vehicles, Budget letters (Box 67)
  - Motor Vehicles, Gasoline prices (Box 67)
  - Motor Vehicles, License tax (Box 67)
  - Motor Vehicles, Police Radio System (Box 67)
  - Motor Vehicles, Safety Conference (Box 67)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors (Box 68)
  - Narcotics Law (Box 68)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs (Box 68)
  - Natural Bridge (Box 68)
  - Natural Resources Development Commission Conference (Box 68)
  - Negroes (Box 68)
  - Newspaper subscriptions (Box 68)
  - Notary Public (Box 68)
  - Office space (Box 68)
  - Office space, New buildings (Box 68)
  - Old Age Pensions (Box 69)
  - Old Age Pensions, Commission (Box 70)
  - Old Age Pensions, Letters and material (Box 70)
  - Orange County Celebration (Box 70)
  - Patrick Henry Bicentennial (Box 70)
  - Peace (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Board (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Advisory Board on Criminal and Mental Hygiene (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Cotton Farm (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Misc. (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Parole Board (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, Prison sentences (Box 70)
  - Penitentiary, State Farm (Box 70)
  - Photographs (Box 71)
  - Pollution (Box 71)
  - Port Authority (Box 71)
  - Port Authority, Davis William Holmes Controversy (Box 71)
  - Portraits (Box 72)
  - Positions, Requests for (Box 72)
  - Potomac Rivers Bridge (Box 72)
  - Potomac Rivers Bridge, Commission (Box 72)
  - President, United States (Box 73)
  - President, United States, Inauguration (Box 73)
  - Proclamations (Box 73)
  - Proclamations, Office copies (Box 73)
  - Programs (Box 74)
  - Prohibition (Box 74)
  - Public Administration Bureau (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Commissioner (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Board (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Industrial Schools (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Jails (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Jails, Reports on Prisoners with Terms over 60 days (Box 74)
  - Public Welfare, Mental cases (Box 75)
  - Public Welfare, Mother's Aid (Box 75)
  - Public Welfare, Public Assistance Division (Box 75)
  - Public Welfare, Service Officer (Box 76)
  - Public Welfare, Veterans Advisory Board (Box 76)
  - Publications, Received (Box 76-77)
  - Publications, Requested (Box 77)
  - Purchase and Printing, Director (Box 77)
  - Purchase and Printing, Printing Division (Box 78)
  - Purchase and Printing, Standardization Board (Box 78)
  - Railroads (Box 78)
  - Real Estate Commission (Box 78)
  - Recommendations (Box 78-79)
  - Red Cross (Box 79)
  - Redistricting (Box 79)
  - Relief (Box 79)
  - Relief (Box 79)
  - Reorganization of State Government (Box 79)
  - Residents, New (Box 79)
  - Richmond Academy of Arts (Box 79)
  - Richmond Bicentennial (Box 79)
  - Richmond Social Service Bureau (Box 79)
  - Richmond Community Fund (Box 79)
  - Richmond Hospital Service Association (Box 79)
  - Richmond Symphony Orchestra (Box 79)
  - Rogers, Will, Memorial (Box 79)
  - Salvation Army (Box 79)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 80)
  - Secretary of the Navy (Box 80)
  - Secretary of the State (Box 80)
  - Secretary of War (Box 80)
  - Social Security (Box 80)
  - Soil Conservation (Box 80)
  - Soldiers' Home (Box 81)
  - Sons of Revolution (Box 81)
  - Southeastern Development Board (Box 81)
  - Spanish American War Veterans (Box 81)
  - State Employers Insurance (Box 81)
  - State Employer Retirement Fund (Box 81)
  - State Flower (Box 81)
  - State Horticultural Society (Box 81)
  - State Office Buildings Commission (Box 81)
  - State Planning Board (Box 81-82)
  - State seal (Box 82)
  - State Teacher's College (Box 82)
  - State Teacher's College, Farmville (Box 82)
  - State Teacher's College, Fredericksburg (Box 82)
  - State Teacher's College, Harrisonburg (Box 82)
  - State Teacher's College, Radford (Box 82)
  - Statements (Box 82-83)
  - Statutory, Research and Drafting (Box 83)
  - Stratford (Box 84)
  - Sunday Blue Laws (Box 84)
  - Tangier Island (Box 84)
  - Taylor Zachary, 150th Anniversary (Box 84)
  - Taxation (Box 84)
  - Taxation, Commissioner (Box 84)
  - Taxation, Sales tax (Box 84)
  - Telegrams (Box 84)
  - Texas Centennial (Box 85)
  - Train, Bus, Hotel schedules (Box 85)
  - Travelers Protection Association (Box 85)
  - Treasurer (Box 85)
  - Treasurer, Recommendations, Jones, Powhatan (Box 85)
  - Treasurer, Recommendations, Misc. (Box 85)
  - Treasurer, Century Bonds (Box 85)
  - Trial Justices (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Recommendations, Cavedo, Frank O. (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Recommendations, Linweaver, Mrs. Ethel I. (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Recommendations, Moseley, H.B. (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Recommendations, Richardson, Mrs. Eudora R. (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Recommendations, Misc. (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Federal approval (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Insurance (Box 86)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Positions (Box 87)
  - Uniform State Laws Commission (Box 87)
  - United States Bureau of Census (Box 87)
  - United States Naval Academy (Box 87)
  - University of Virginia (Box 87)
  - University of Virginia, Board (Box 87)
  - Vacation (Box 87)
  - Valentine, Lila Meade, Tablet (Box 87)
  - Valley Forge (Box 87)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 87)
  - Virginia Commission for the Blind (Box 87)
  - Virginia Industrial Farm for Women (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial Schools (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial Schools, Board (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Boys (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Children (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls (Box 88)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Girls (Box 88)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School for Boys (Box 88)
  - Virginia-Maryland Boundary (Box 88)
  - Virginia Military Institute (Box 88)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 88-89)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Contributions (Box 89)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History (Box 89)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 89)
  - Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 89)
  - Virginia Extension Division (Box 89)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind (Box 90)
  - Virginia State College for Blacks (Box 91)
  - Virginia State Employment Service (Box 91)
  - Virginia Fair Association (Box 91)
  - Virginia Horticultural Society (Box 91)
  - Virginia School for Black Deaf and Blind (Box 91)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 91)
  - Virginia Tuberculosis Association (Box 91)
  - Virginia Women's Council (Box 91)
  - War Memorial Commission (Box 91)
  - Washington, George (Box 91)
  - Washington, George, Houdon statue (Box 91)
  - Washington, George, Memorial parkway (Box 91)
  - Washington, George, Mt. Vernon Memorial Highway (Box 91)
  - West Point (Box 92)
  - William and Mary College (Box 92)
  - William and Mary College, Foster matter (Box 92)
  - Williams, John W., Memorial Fund (Box 92)
  - Williamsburg, General Assembly meeting (Box 92)
  - Williamsburg, Restoration (Box 92)
  - Williamsburg, Sewage Disposal Plant (Box 92)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Memorial (Box 92)
  - Wine-Liquor Regional Board (Box 92)
  - Workman's Compensation Bureau (Box 92)
  - World's Fair (Box 92)
  - W.R.V.A. (Box 92)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 92)
  - Young Democrats Club (Box 92)
  - Youth Administration (Box 92)
  - Youth Administration, National (Box 92)
- Series II. General Assembly, 1934-1938., Extent: 4 cu. ft. [8 boxes]. (Box 93-100)
  The General Assembly records are housed in 8 boxes and are arranged by session.
  - 1934 Session (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Address (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Billboards (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Bills not signed (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Bills sent back (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Bills signed (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Boxing Bill (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Jarnette Sanatorium Bill (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, House Bill 231 (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Messages (Box 93)
  - 1934 Session, Milk Bill (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Milk Control Board (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Notes on Bills (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Racing Law (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Radio Bill (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Railway and Bus matters (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Redistricting (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Senate Bill 309 (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, South Norfolk Charter Bill (Box 94)
  - 1934 Session, Special Session, Need of (Box 95)
  - 1934 Session, Tax Bill (Box 95)
  - 1935, Correspondence (Box 95)
  - 1935, Billboards (Box 95)
  - 1935, Jails (Box 95)
  - 1935, Special Session (Box 95)
  - 1936 Session (Box 95)
  - 1936 Session, Bills signed (Box 95)
  - 1936 Session, Budget Conference (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Child Conservation (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Fire Prevention (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Message material (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Messages (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Notes on bills (Box 96)
  - 1936 Session, Old Age Pension (Box 96-97)
  - 1936 Session, Reception (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Recommendations (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Reports on Departments (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Salary Restoration (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Sales tax (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Schools (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Special messages (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, State Highway Patrol (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, State Scholarships (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Tea for Wives (Box 97)
  - 1936 Session, Tobacco Bill (Box 97)
  - 1936 Special Session, Bills signed (Box 98)
  - 1936 Special Session, Notes on bills (Box 98)
  - 1936 Special Session, Reception (Box 98)
  - 1936 Special Session, Special messages (Box 98)
  - 1938 Session, Alcohol, Report on Effects of (Box 98)
  - 1938 Session, Budget Conference (Box 99)
  - 1938 Session, Message, Reports from Departments (Box 99)
  - 1938 Session, Petition regarding Senate Bill 107 and 109 (Box 99-100)
  - 1938 Session, Reception (Box 100)
  - 1938 Session, Tuberculosis (Box 100)
- Series III. Reports on Audits, 1934-1938., Extent: 14 cu. ft. [28 boxes]. (Box 100-127)
  The Reports on Audits are housed in 28 boxes and are divided into three subseries: Cities and Towns, Counties, and State Agencies.
  - Subseries A. Cities and Towns
    - Alexandria (Box 100)
    - Berryville (Box 100)
    - Bristol (Box 100)
    - Buena Vista (Box 100)
    - Charlottesville (Box 100)
    - Chatham (Box 100)
    - Clifton Forge (Box 100)
    - Danville (Box 101)
    - Fredericksburg (Box 101)
    - Hopewell (Box 101)
    - Kenbridge (Box 101)
    - Kilmarnock (Box 101)
    - Lynchburg (Box 101)
    - New Market (Box 101)
    - Newport News (Box 101)
    - Norton (Box 101)
    - Orange (Box 101)
    - Petersburg (Box 101)
    - Portsmouth (Box 101)
    - Radford (Box 101)
    - Richmond (Box 101)
    - Roanoke (Box 101)
    - Staunton (Box 101)
    - Strasburg (Box 101)
    - Suffolk (Box 101)
    - Winchester (Box 101)
    - Wise (Box 101)
  - Subseries B. Counties
    - Accomack County (Box 102)
    - Albemarle County (Box 102)
    - Alleghany County (Box 102)
    - Amelia County (Box 102)
    - Amherst County (Box 103)
    - Appomattox County (Box 103)
    - Arlington County (Box 103)
    - Augusta County (Box 103)
    - Bath County (Box 103)
    - Bedford County (Box 103)
    - Bland County (Box 104)
    - Botetourt County (Box 104)
    - Brunswick County (Box 104)
    - Buchanan County (Box 104)
    - Buckingham County (Box 104)
    - Campbell County (Box 104-105)
    - Caroline County (Box 105)
    - Carroll County (Box 105)
    - Charles CIty County (Box 105)
    - Charlotte County (Box 105)
    - Chesterfield County (Box 105)
    - Clark County (Box 106)
    - Craig County (Box 106)
    - Culpeper County (Box 106)
    - Cumberland County (Box 106)
    - Dickenson County (Box 106-107)
    - Dinwiddie County (Box 107)
    - Elizabeth City County (Box 107)
    - Essex County (Box 107)
    - Fairfax County (Box 107)
    - Fauquier County (Box 107)
    - Floyd County (Box 107-108)
    - Fluvanna County (Box 108)
    - Franklin County (Box 108)
    - Frederick County (Box 108)
    - Giles County (Box 108)
    - Gloucester County (Box 108)
    - Goochland County (Box 108)
    - Grayson County (Box 109)
    - Greene County (Box 109)
    - Greensville County (Box 109)
    - Halifax County (Box 109)
    - Hanover County (Box 109)
    - Henrico County (Box 109-110)
    - Henry County (Box 110)
    - Highland County (Box 110)
    - Isle of Wight County (Box 110)
    - James City County (Box 110)
    - King and Queen County (Box 110)
    - King George County (Box 110)
    - King William County (Box 111)
    - Lancaster County (Box 111)
    - Lee County (Box 111)
    - Loudoun County (Box 111)
    - Louisa County (Box 112)
    - Lunenburg County (Box 112)
    - Madison County (Box 112)
    - Mathews County (Box 112)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box 112)
    - Middlesex County (Box 112)
    - Montgomery County (Box 112)
    - Nansemond County (Box 113)
    - Nelson County (Box 113)
    - New Kent County (Box 113)
    - Norfolk County (Box 113)
    - Northumberland County (Box 113)
    - Northampton County (Box 114)
    - Nottoway County (Box 114)
    - Orange County (Box 114)
    - Page County (Box 114)
    - Patrick County (Box 114)
    - Pittsylvania County (Box 115)
    - Powhatan County (Box 115)
    - rince Edward County (Box 115)
    - Prince George County (Box 115)
    - Prince William County (Box 115)
    - Princess Anne County (Box 116)
    - Pulaski County (Box 116)
    - Rappahannock County (Box 116)
    - Richmond County (Box 116)
    - Roanoke County (Box 116)
    - Rockbridge County (Box 116-117)
    - Rockingham County (Box 117)
    - Russell County (Box 117)
    - Scott County (Box 117)
    - Shenandoah County (Box 117)
    - Smyth County (Box 117)
    - Southampton County (Box 117)
    - Spotsylvania County (Box 117)
    - Stafford County (Box 117)
    - Surry County (Box 117)
    - Sussex County (Box 118)
    - Tazewell County (Box 118)
    - Warren County (Box 118)
    - Warwick County (Box 118)
    - Washington County (Box 118)
    - Westmoreland County (Box 118)
    - Wise County (Box 118-119)
    - Wythe County (Box 119)
    - York County (Box 119)
  - Subseries C. State Agencies
    - Accountancy (Box 119)
    - Agriculture and Immigration (Box 119)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 119-120)
    - Art Museum (Box 120)
    - Attorney General (Box 120)
    - Budget (Box 121)
    - Clerk, House of Delegates (Box 121)
    - Conservation and Development Commission (Box 121)
    - Corporation Commission (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Medical College of Virginia (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Teachers College, Farmouth (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Teachers College, Fredericksburg (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Teachers College, Harrisonburg (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Teachers College, Radford (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Virginia Military Institute (Box 121)
    - Education, Board of, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 122)
    - Education, Board of, Virginia School for Colored Deaf and Blind (Box 122)
    - Education, Board of, Virginia School for Deaf and Blind (Box 122)
    - Education, Board of, Virginia State College for Negroes (Box 122)
    - Education, Board of, William and Mary (Box 122)
    - Emergency Relief Administration (Box 123-124)
    - Examiners Board of Graduate Nurses (Box 124)
    - Fee Commission (Box 124)
    - Fisheries Commission (Box 124)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries Commission (Box 124)
    - Governor's Advisory Legislative Council (Box 124)
    - Governor's Office (Box 124)
    - Grounds and Buildings (Box 124)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Blue Ridge Sanatorium (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Catawba Sanatorium (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Central State Hospital (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Eastern State Hospital (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Home for Needy Confederate Women (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, R.E. Lee Camp Soldier's Home (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Piedmont Sanatorium (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Southwestern State Hospital (Box 125)
    - Health and Vital Statistics, Western State Hospital (Box 125)
    - Highways (Box 125)
    - Legislative Council (Box 125)
    - Legislative Drafting Bureau (Box 125)
    - Library (Box 125)
    - Markets, Division of (Box 125)
    - Medical Examiners (Box 125)
    - Military Affairs (Box 125)
    - Motor Vehicles (Box 125)
    - Motion Picture Censors (Box 125)
    - Planning Board (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Board (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Industrial Farm for Women (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Industrial School for Boys (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Industrial School for Colored Boys (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Industrial School for Girls (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, Penitentiary (Box 126)
    - Public Welfare, State Farms (Box 126)
    - Purchase and Printing (Box 126)
    - Real Estate Commission (Box 126)
    - Shenandoah National Park Fund (Box 126)
    - Sinking Fund (Box 126)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals, Staunton (Box 126)
    - Taxation (Box 126)
    - Treasurer (Box 126)
    - Virginia Commission for the Blind (Box 126)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 126)
    - War Memorial Commission (Box 126)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Box 126)
    - Works Progress Administration (Box 127)
- Series IV. Financial Affairs, 1934-1938., Extent: 1.5 cu. ft. [3 boxes]. (Box 127-129)
  The Financial Affairs records are housed in 3 boxes and are arranged by Executive Control number.
  - Executive Control 121-01 (Box 127)
  - Executive Control 121-01, Purchase Orders (Box 127)
  - Executive Control 121-01, Vendor's Invoices (Box 127-128)
  - Executive Control 121-02 (Box 128)
  - Executive Control 121-02, Purchase Orders (Box 128)
  - Executive Control 121-02, Vendor's Invoices (Box 128-129)
  - Executive Control 121-15 (Box 129)
  - Executive Control 121-15, Purchase Orders (Box 129)
  - Executive Control 121-15, Vendor's Invoices (Box 129)
  - Executive Control 837-01 (Box 129)
  - Executive Control 837-01, Purchase Orders (Box 129)
  - Executive Control 837-01, Vendor's Invoices (Box 129)
- Series V. Power Plant Maintenance, 1934-1938., Extent: 1.5 cu. ft. [3 boxes]. (Box 129-132)
  The Power Plant Maintenance records are housed in 3 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by state institution, with information on coal first.
  - Coal (Box 129)
  - Coal, Analysis (Box 130)
  - Coal, Budget Director (Box 130)
  - Coal, Pamphlets (Box 130)
  - Coal, Contracts (Box 130)
  - Coal, Tests (Box 130)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Blue Ridge Sanatorium (Box 130)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Catawba Sanatorium (Box 130)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Eastern State Hospital (Box 130)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Farmville State Teacher's College (Box 131)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Fish Hatcher (Box 131)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Fredericksburg State Teacher's College (Box 131-132)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Piedmont Sanatorium (Box 132)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Piedmont Sanatorium (Box 132)
  - Power plants in state institutions, Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls (Box 132)
  - Power plants in state institutions, University of Virginia (Box 132)
- Series VI. Penal Affairs, 1934-1938., Extent: 11 cu. ft. [21 boxes]. (Box 133-153)
  The Penal Affairs records are housed in 21 boxes and are arranged by Applications for Restoration of Driving Licenses, History of Convictions, Extraditions, and Pardons.
  - Applications for Restoration of Driver's Licenses, Driving under the influence (Box 133-134)
  - Applications for Restoration of Driver's Licenses, Reckless Driving (Box 134)
  - Applications for Restoration of Driver's Licenses, Williams H.H. (Box 134)
  - Convictions, History of, Reports (Box 134-135)
  - Convictions, History of, Survey (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, Miscellaneous (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, Foreign countries (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, Model papers (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, Other states (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, Rules and regulations (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, State police to aid local officials (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, A (Box 136)
  - Extraditions, B (Box 136-137)
  - Extraditions, C (Box 137)
  - Extraditions, Crawford, George (Box 138)
  - Extraditions, D (Box 138)
  - Extraditions, Davis, Kyle C. (Box 138)
  - Extraditions, E (Box 138)
  - Extraditions, F (Box 138)
  - Extraditions, F (Box 139)
  - Extraditions, G (Box 139)
  - Extraditions, I (Box 139)
  - Extraditions, J (Box 139-140)
  - Extraditions, K (Box 140)
  - Extraditions, L (Box 140)
  - Extraditions, Mc (Box 140)
  - Extraditions, M (Box 141)
  - Extraditions, N (Box 141)
  - Extraditions, O (Box 141)
  - Extraditions, P (Box 141)
  - Extraditions, Q (Box 142)
  - Extraditions, R (Box 142)
  - Extraditions, S (Box 142)
  - Extraditions, T (Box 143)
  - Extraditions, U (Box 143)
  - Extraditions, V (Box 143)
  - Extraditions, W (Box 143)
  - Extraditions, X, Y, Z (Box 143)
  - Pardons, Jail prisoners requests (Box 143)
  - Pardons, Penitential prisoners' requests (Box 144)
  - Pardons, Adams-Candle (Box 144)
  - Pardons, Carter-Harvell (Box 145)
  - Pardons, Hickman-Joyce (Box 146)
  - Pardons, Kaufman-Morton (Box 147)
  - Pardons, Mullens-Smith (Box 148)
  - Pardons, Snead-Watson (Box 149)
  - Pardons, Weeks-Zimmerman (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Bankers case (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Federal (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Good Conduct Allowances (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Miscellaneous (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Other states (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Card files (Box 150-153)
  - Rewards (Box 153)
- Series VII. Federal Government, 1934-1938., Extent: 4.5 cu. ft. [9 boxes]. (Box 154)
  The Federal Government records are housed in 9 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by topic or agency. Subjects include: Agricultural Adjustment Act, Emergency Relief Administration, Public Works Administration, Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Resettlement Administration, and Works Progress Administration.